# DARYL **BLOUGH**

West Midlands · 07598123680 darylxcuf@gmail.com

I am a hard-working, motivated and enthusiastic Office Administrator with experience in Customer Service, Data Entry, Logistics and Project Management. I always strive to achieve the highest standard possible at any given task or in any situation. I am accustomed to working in a challenging and fast-paced environment, particularly when dealing with multiple projects and priorities at the same time.

# **SKILLS**

- Experienced in working with a team in leadership and management roles.
- Enjoy customer interactions and delivering quality experience to clients.
- Passion for data entry.
- High level of attention to detail.
- Ability to work without supervision.
- Capable in handling confidential material.

- Excellent communication skills.
- Strong computer skills, typing speed and IT knowledge.
- Proficient working in the Microsoft Office suit programs including Excel, Word, Outlook, Access, PowerPoint.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **OCT 2019 – CURRENT**

## **OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR, PAKISTAN CONSULATE**

- Oversaw customer service and phone helpline.
- Operated a live chat with customers and clients.
- Experience in sales and brand promotion.
- Purchased office supplies.
- Document filing and record upkeep including handling confidential material.
- Updated and maintained data entry and company records.
- Arranged and booked travel and hotel accommodation for senior government officials.
- Oversaw office upgrade projects including CCTV installation, Storage cleanout, building maintenance and disposal of sensitive documents.
- Met and exceeded monthly targets and goals.

#### OCT 2018 - OCT 2019

# LOGISTICS/STOCK CONTROL, SHAFTEC AUTOMOTIVE COMPONENTS LTD.

- Managed stock levels and updated the company software to account for defects, returns, over shipped stock and under shipped stock.
- Performed monthly stock counts to ensure the records were up to date and adjusted them if needed.
- Handled incoming customer returns, always dealing with them courteously and professionally while keeping strictly to the companies return policies.
- Updated and maintained data entry and company records
- Data entry and analysis

#### JUN 2017 - OCT 2018

## **LOGISTICS, SAMARITANS PURSE**

- Researched materials and items for the housing construction.
- Met with distributers to gain quotes on material sourcing.
- Arranged for house building materials to be delivered to the correct location.
- Wrote up reports on the progress of specific house building projects.
- Weekly reports to the manager on the progress, cost, time, and availability of the projects I was sourcing materials for and overseeing.
- Kept detailed records and logs of company purchases
- Data entry and analysis on company performance and KPI

# **EDUCATION**

**JUN 2017** 

HIGHSCHOOL DIPLOMA, THE MOUNT ACADEMY

Graduated from The Mount Academy in New York with 28.5 credits and a 3.77 GPA

#### REFERENCES

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST